chiisa na yakusoku mo
You couldn’t even keep a small promise
mamorenai kara
ooki na akubi de
And you just glossed over it with a big yawn
gomaka shite ita na
chiisa na shiawase mo
I couldn’t find even a small bit of happiness
mitsukerarenai kara
ooki na me kara namida o
So tears were falling from my big eyes
nagashiteta na
itoshii dake ja tarinai shi
Because just being loved isn’t enough
ureshii dake ja fuan da shi
And because only being happy makes me uneasy
yasashii dake ja imi nai shi
And because when there’s only kindness, it’s meaningless,
tsurete itte ageru kara
I’ll take you with me,
yuyuyuyuyu, sansan
Miserable, miserable brilliance
hanasanaide ite kureru nara
Don’t let us be separated, because I’ll do anything for you
nandemo kanaete ageru kara~
tsurete itte ageru kara
I’ll take you with me,
yuyuyuyuyu, sansan
Miserable, miserable brilliance
hanasanaide ite kureru nara
Don’t let us be separated, because I’ll do anything for you
nandemo kanaete ageru~ kara
kore kara atashi-tachi
From now on, I wonder what we’ll become
dou naru no ka na
ima doudemoii koto
Right now, I’m thinking that it probably doesn’t matter
kangaeteta desho
nikushimi dake ja kiri nai shi
Because when there’s nothing but hatred, it won’t end
kanashii dake ja fuman da shi
And because I’m not satisfied with just sadness
kibishii dake ja eminai shi
And because when we’re nothing but strict with each other, we don’t smile,
tsurete itte ageru kara
I’ll take you with me, so come over this way, darling
kocchi ni oide yo darling
hanasanaide ite kureru nara
Don’t let us be separated, because I’ll always forgive you
itsudemo yurushite ageru kara~
tsurete itte ageru kara
I’ll take you with me, so come over this way, darling
kocchi ni oide yo darling
hanasanaide ite kureru nara
Don’t let us be separated, because I’ll always forgive you
itsudemo yurushite ageru~ kara
dokonidemo
Anywhere, anywhere, anywhere
doko ni itemo
As long as we’re together somewhere
tsurete itte ageru kara…
I’ll take you with me, so…
hanasanaide ite kureru nara…
If you don’t let us get separated…
tsurete itte ageru kara
I’ll take you with me,
yuyuyuyuyu, sansan
Miserable, miserable brilliance
hanasanaide ite kureru nara
Don’t let us be separated, because I’ll do anything for you
nandemo kanaete ageru kara~
tsurete itte ageru kara
I’ll take you with me,
yuyuyuyuyu, sansan
Miserable, miserable brilliance
hanasanaide ite kureru nara
Don’t let us be separated, because I’ll do anything for you
nandemo kanaete ageru~ kara